5.
Today,
please feel free to ask any questions in
the chat in Q&
A or only just raise your hand.
And today we have the kick off session
which we will.
Be led by woba,
Clichevich Director AA Solution
Technologies Hello Woba and I think that
we can start.
Yeah, let me start so.
Uh,
we starting this like first of all we
starting these in kind of.
Crazy mode because like if you would do
this these kind of regular rules,
it would require part time for
preparation, building some scenarios,
recordings, whatever it's needed like.
But that's what we wouldn't start it at
all, I would say,
because now we're really living in crazy,
crazy mode,
so a lot of activities in parallel,
et cetera.
So that's why everything what we are
doing here will be in real time.
Usually I'm not preparing.
I have some ideas.
What we are going to discuss.
So that's why like we started from it.
This is important for everyone is to
understand that like if you want to have
prepared training,
so just go to learnings,
find some trainings,
learn there so it's approved, prepared,
validated several times, but not sure.
If it's up to date, yes.
So that's why like it's your ways and to
learn here we we are going to do
something something what we are doing
every day but for peak audience so.
It's probably will be some first slides
and you will never see the presentations
again. Thanks for Ira about this.
Basically what we are going to do.
So I hope everyone saw the video in the
nice page what again Ira did build.
For this about AI native team who did not
participate in AI conference and AI
native future talk.
So just please take a look on this to get
better understanding how that work works
and.
Like technically,
technically I did build everything what
you saw in the video alone.
Like some all technical aspects,
adoption aspects and other things like
talk to people, scale things up, etc.
Usually it's part of for other people who.
Who better likes the job like Kira.
So usually IR is talking to people in
Post ML to scale up the solutions,
but technical aspects was done by me.
So that's for like again like if you're
talking about kind of this.
Meeting and every single will be behind
of it. It will be technical.
So if you're afraid coding,
so you still can do this,
but probably you will have some
challenges because I think you you need
to understand high level solution.
Do not approve something what the I do by
mistake.
So that's why it's important to
understand that it will be also technical.
Yeah,
so I will try to deep dive to all details,
try to explain to you everything what I
know. So just my knowledge,
my personal experience.
To be honest,
not a lot of theoretical data in my head,
but a lot of practical.
What is important to understand again,
we did have some holy war several days
ago in some chat did put in the red and
will give you one minute to think about
it.
So for people who is not reading the
slides now like everything.
What is in the chat and the chat will be
open for everyone.
So we also building community where you
you're free,
you're free to ask me any questions so I
I will try to support you,
but I want to say that everything in this
chat.
Also on the sessions what we are going to
make will be processed by AI.
After the talk today I will put it
transcript to AI and I will build some
knowledge base based on this.
So like again,
if you ask questions in the chat,
I will process them with AI as well and
probably even AI will answer the
questions for you from my.
Let's say from my account.
So like just for you like to be sure that
personal data like your names etc.
If you're afraid of this,
it's not this topic, not for you.
You're not ready for AI native approach
what we are going to show.
So sorry about it,
but like just disconnect from the call,
go to do some production activities.
Like earn some money,
whatever else you want to do,
drink coffee as well. So just important,
everything will be processed by AI,
including your names.
I'm not talking about titles or whatever,
but your names, yes.
So because for me I'm too lazy to filter
out it from from from the messages before
putting it to LLM.
LLM will be DL but overall under the DL
but you need to understand it.
Just come for this code in the chat.
I hope it will be not closed after the
call, but anyway if it will be closed,
I think we will create new one and we
will share the link by mail,
but scan it and join.
Do not afraid to ask questions,
Everything will be OK.
discuss any topics.
Oh, I trust you. But by some reasons,
we never saw chats after the calls. Yeah,
Yeah.
OK. And as I, as I said at the beginning,
we don't promise anything. Yeah. So like,
if tomorrow, by some reasons,
we will not have time.
Uh, we can just stop the sessions. Uh,
because of other activities.
I hope it will not happen, but anyway, um.
I'm sorry to meet you able to mute you so,
but anyway I will try to give you as
maximum as I can from my practical
experience. This is main goal.
Try to scale my brain,
my brain to to you and also in scope of
the sessions.
I also want to build my own PB about me
about what?
Things what I know which you can use then
like knowledge base,
you will be able to chat with me without
me, let's say.
So it's also important and for you to
understand why everything will be
recorded,
why we want to bring the AI native
approach from the beginning.
Any questions before we start?
While I will drink a bit coffee,
feel free to raise.
Cool.
Are you all still real or I I generated?
I did have idea but I did not have time.
I have idea but by the way like we can
try to.
I'm not sure how technically it can be
done like I mean I have idea really
prerecorded and like try to share and
then just make some questionnaire to
understand like will you get that I am
real or not.
So probably we'll do this,
but like if you will not see me talking
in the team so you will understand that
I'm not real.
Yeah so but if I will talk in slides so
it's like but now it's also possible by
the way if you have that questions how to
make it so like it's also part of the
talk and one more thing we forgot to.
Say I will show my experience based on
most popular tools,
but if you do same things with your tools,
for instance I will use cursor,
you will use, you can use Copilot.
And you're doing same similar.
You can then talk to me,
talk to IRA and also just go to the
session and share your experience instead
of me.
So that's something what you also want to
build.
You want to build strong community with
experts who is expert in SDLC.
Agentic building and everything what is
around these.
This is what I'm looking for and this is
important and forgot to say that at the
end yes you will have homework but it's
up to you when you do this and.
So like the idea that you will repeat
what I did.
Like 1 to one,
I expect first of all the some video.
I I will support you as I can. Yeah.
So there is now 190 people on the call,
but we also introduced the GitHub.
And I will try to support you with AI and
without.
So basically if you do build it at the
end you will get the badge special
special badge which means that you did
pass the course you let's say you has.
Some you have some skills in let's say AI
technology solutions and this is can be
really valuable sign for for if you
decide to let's say join to this new role
which we didn't introduce in the pump,
it will be really good sign.
On the assessment.
So this is also what I wanted to to to
say. If you did build this already,
just do not wait right in direct and we
can have extra session because.
There is already demand and requests on
such people like me and who who can do
this in real life. All right,
I'm stopping sharing today will be boring
session.
But will be important.
And we are going with you.
OK, before I'm starting, raise your hand,
let's see.
Who is who?
Who has project management skills?
OK.
Cool 26.
Uh, and let's say raise your hands. Who?
Who? Who is leading the projects?
Just like, uh, definitely.
OK, it's it's more good. Last question,
I hope the rest is kind of solution
architects, chips at et cetera.
So but let's see why I did ask.
Because today I will focus really on
project management,
so because it is important to understand.
Process.
More important to understand small pieces
of this process.
Who did work with me on Liberty Global
Account?
They need to know structures what I'm
using when I'm doing project management
or delivery management in account.
Today I'm going to show something like
the same structure which I did built with
Opus model.
Which is applicable for most of the use
cases.
Just put to your heads several things
like if I'm talking about JIRA,
that means I'm talking about tracker.
Tracker for you it's something.
Where we just store tasks, packs, stories,
features, epics, whatever.
This is tracker.
In our case I will use Jira because it's
most popular tool,
but if I'm talking about Jira is the same
applicable for others like Rally,
Azure DevOps.
Jira server, Jira cloud,
what else we have? Target process,
probably something what they forgot,
but I think I did mention most important
one then also like source code.
We will use GitHub,
but when I'm talking about source code,
like I'm I'm talking about services which
is hosting source code. It can be GitHub,
it can be GitLab, it can be Bitbucket.
I don't know what else we have.
I hope nothing else,
but I'm talking about this.
And that's it. Runners. Yeah,
so like Archestrator for for for runners.
It's again on GitHub, GitLab, Bitbuckets.
They have on runners, let's say,
but also you can use Jenkins for instance
if you have your Jenkins loaded in place.
If by some reason you don't know words
what I just said, so.
Please try to understand.
Maybe you will get them at the end and
learning path is also important to see.
All right.
Let me share my screen. OK,
I'm zoom out by reason.
This is kind of again,
I just did find this what I spent like
several hours with Opus.
To discuss what we can do from structures,
yeah,
and that we are going to use now and we
are going to build this ourselves in Jira.
If you have questions during the talk,
just stop me, please raise your question.
So it's important.
We we are going to use Jira.
I will use my playground Jira.
So here I have two projects I think and
we are going to create new one just for
our purposes because again I did promise
to start everything from the beginning.
That's why we will create new one.
We will have conference,
but the way you see that it was high
level diagram created,
I don't remember when July, yes, many,
many months ago if you're talking in
timeline of AI.
We will use cursor.
We will have GitHub.
That's it.
I think it's it should be enough for
everything what what I'm going to show
you during the full course.
So for experiments with videos like I can
switch for sure for LLMS like Gemini for
for TL etcetera,
but it's kind of let's say direct access
to.
Yeah, but overall from tools perspective,
we are going to use everything what what
I did show in AI native video to to build
this.
Let's try and start from the beginning.
You see project management.
When I did have discussion with Oppos,
we did agree to have 33 levels.
Epic story sub task.
Again in ideal scenario you need to have
three layers in hierarchy.
How to build it? It's it does not matter.
I mean like you can have separate
projects for for them or you can have
everything in one project and manage this.
Is issue types or you can have even
prefixes.
If you're not lucky and customer does not
allow it, you can have just labels, yeah,
but overall you should have this
structure and I will show this also in an
example here just because.
I I show reality.
I have exactly the same like I have epic
level, story level,
there is box as well and under the story
we have there is subtasks.
Um.
Interesting. Raise your hands.
Maybe who has similar structure in your
projects?
OK, great.
Zen.
Let's start from that side.
Issue types.
I'm sorry.
Just closed. OK, issue types.
Provides.
That's not to work.
OK, let's go here.
We we can have like following structure
epic story.
Story estimations must be limited.
80 sorting story points.
It's maximum even I would say.
Eight should be maximum at current moment.
Even if it is 8,
we already need to think about agent
which will do the composition for us.
Just try to remember your current sprints
and think.
How many times you did story which is 8
story points,
let's say or 13 within one Sprint.
Don't see hands,
but I I I hope I am right. Yeah.
So basically, OK, Sasha has that's good.
Sasha has pretty cool developers or he's
overestimate because he wants to show
better velocity for customer.
That's also fine, in short.
My observations that AI usually can do
everything what is less than 8 story
points from one iteration.
That's why it's important to understand
the decomposition of the process and for
Yeah.
for guys who is orchestrate, yeah.
For both.
Over we have some technical problem. Yeah,
video and screen sharing to stock.
OK.
I think that please restart.
You know you your laptop cannot help you
here.
Do we see screen?
Yeah.
I hope yes.
Please click C browser with mermaid chart.
Yeah, we do. We do.
We do.
OK cool. So basically this is important.
Yeah let let let me show you practically
and also there is special epic like UI
components for style guide and also for
for UI in reality then subtasks.
Queue for questions and decisions.
You need to have a place where you ask
questions. By the way,
if you don't have this practical in your
team yet,
just try to introduce it when people
cannot ask questions in direct,
but they need to ask questions in in.
Tickets in Limberty global we did have it.
So then solution design for API because I
have API model UI UI model.
I also do have core for core model.
Yes there is legacy I think documentation
so there is no SD.
So then core API UI for implementation
tickets, so like tree models.
I'm showing that this structure
applicable also for multi models
architecture.
Yeah and the UI comfort style guide
components.
Basically this structure then allows you
and if you go back to the Jira where you
can see that epic story.
Question is the API API is the UI UI.
So that means that was affected server
model was some question and was affected
UI model for development.
So there is also a style guide for UI
which is which was created based on the
code by the way.
So it was also kind of experiment to
restore everything that I do have in the
code back to the JIRA because JIRA needs
to have external status.
So there is also like foundation.
We have multiple prefixes here now like
foundation, atoms, molecules, assets,
navigation, organisms.
So there is more Organism, guide,
animation, layout, molecules, yeah.
So then we also can expand it and find
base colors, accent colors,
et cetera if I open it.
We also can see colors,
even with some colors, tables,
how to use it, etcetera.
So this is what was restored back from
from the code. Like I did have a code,
I did write MCP for Jira for my tools and
I did restore it from the code.
So.
But this is needed for yes again.
We have some questions from Zahar Zahar,
welcome.
Uh, OK.
Actually not any urgent question.
I just wanted to ask kind of how much are
you insisting that every type of question
is the subtask or why not questions that
can be asked and answered in the comments?
Because most of the systems that we're
using they have comments and if I have a.
Kind of a feature task and so on.
Why not to consolidate the whole
discussion into the comments under it?
Great question.
Uh.
Great question. So let me try to answer.
Why we have this decomposition?
The power is in filters and JQL because I
can get all questions from JQL.
I can also mark questions as relevant or
irrelevant.
I can give answer and for instance some
questions.
Can be also same in the real life.
Some questions can be blockers for start
feature, some questions can be parked,
some questions can have extensive
discussion.
So that's why like in also in Liberty
Global,
we definitely had like all tickets and
questions, so in Postml.
Sometimes guys do use it, sometimes not,
but overall that really gives you.
First of all,
you have decompositions of your question.
You can exactly understand what is
blocking you, what is not.
If you have fixed price,
it's super favorite part.
You can have separate workflow where.
Customer needs to approve decisions.
We did have use cases when like customers
did approve decisions and then they
wanted to change decisions and we did
refer to the question ticket where the
decisions was done and then we did raise
change request.
Because they did change their mind.
So like and it's also really important
for for tracking purposes.
Let me show you if I let some some latest
one I think here latest I did develop a
connector for teams.
Yes.
Teams you see, by the way,
when you switch to latest model you you
you'll get a much better.
12 this one.
Well,
I'm afraid the screen sharing is stuck
again.
Or we just see the Jira if if this is
another screen.
Former.
And we lost tomorrow at all.
Yeah, well, uh, completely.
Did you?
That's an evidence that we're talking to
AI and now AI is overloaded and kind of
requires a long time for processing until
until he comes back.
Contact is already heated.
That's clear AI.
No,
I think that Volvo started a lot of
agents and his laptop.
Cannot. Cannot do it, yeah.
Simply then.
Yeah,
that's the the the there is even a name
for it when you run 20 MCP servers and
then obviously you're running out of
memory.
So laptop will be rebooted because you
launched too many MCP servers.
Now we need now we need here ad break and
advertising should come from Kodami.
Showing that, hey guys, if you use Codeme,
nothing like this happens because Codeme
basically encapsulates all your MCP
servers,
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
put them into the cloud and then your
computer is uncluttered from that stuff.
So guys from Codeme use this opportunity
to to advertise your product.
Yeah.
OK, cool. I did restart teams.
I hope now it's better.
Yeah.
We thought you restarted your laptop
because it's dying on the agency running.
I'm not in this.
OK, but it's a good, good sign.
You know that I'm real today. Yeah, so.
Well,
actually the conjecture was quite
opposite.
OK, that's also interesting.
So you see the team story.
It was certain story points and it was
not done by the way from first iteration
in the way as I wanted to get it,
but it was done by the way connector was
implemented from the first scene.
So let's see you see that this story with
authentification.
Because like it's a bit crazy one write
messages configuration set up which is
almost OK.
So there is also AI did use Python
example what I did right in the it's the
first just to check approach if I even
can read something or I can I write
something to teams.
So you see,
I just did attach here files and I did
ask my to prepare as a story description
and then write solution.
So for for guys who still do not believe
that it works, yes,
so like it works and you can see the
questions here.
And it's pretty interesting.
So like authentification methods for
instance,
because Microsoft has different one and
that it suggests this this option like
device code on browser based.
So and at the end we support option A and
option B. Option A is needed for running.
Like CLAI for option B it's like so and I
understand this this question by the way
like it it can block development and it's
really important to answer.
So same for others.
So you see that all questions marked as
done if the question would be.
Or is like let's say by mistake I would
mark it like irrelevant because that
gives me opportunity easy to then to
build also knowledge base for AI.
You see labels queue all questions here
and I can say like and status in
irrelevant.
And this is irrelevant questions and this
is metrics what probably you would ask me.
OK is asking question but probably it
asks stupid questions like you just show
Yeah.
the magic but which does not work.
I can say like OK guys we have 5
irrelevant questions because in the case.
I did not look to the code base to ask it,
so I needed to understand how it works,
but it didn't.
So that's why like all time when you're
building agent,
it must be simple and all time you need
to understand.
How you collect positive examples and
negative examples from agent,
how how you can market,
how you can collect.
And by the way I forgot to mention in the
beginning you see the reporter which is
also important part.
It is AI Teammate go go to it's my my
mailbox, go to Gmail,
create your AI Teammate account.
So like we're in Post ML.
We did ask to create a distribution list
like AI Teammate Post ML.
So in APAM for instance,
it could be AI teammateapam.
com because you need to understand what
is written in JIRA or in the code by AI
in fully autonomous mode and when it's
written by you. It's really important.
So because here I like if I look into the
question I can see.
Yeah,
I did create it so you will not see this
in history,
but you you can see that I just provided
answer decision here.
I even now want to simplify my life.
So now it creates question with
placeholder for decision because again we
have the issue types for questions.
Templates, yes.
Why we have this?
So basically, yes, go ahead please.
We have a question.
Yeah, well, sorry,
I I have a really dummy question,
but yeah, to step to have a step back,
these questions are actually created.
The issue types in JIRA are created by AI
team made based on the description that
you provided to them, right?
OK.
So this is basically what end,
end the call, OK.
And the code and the code code other
questions if you want questions which is
Mm-hmm.
like basically it depending on me.
What to put to the agent at current
moment?
Context when agent is raising the
questions, it's my initial description.
Let's see my initial description for the
Microsoft Teams. I I will show you.
Uh, OK, yes, this one.
That what I did ask.
Mhm.
Based on this description,
AI is we we starting two agents to
important also for you to understand to
to to simplify agent as much as possible.
Each agent needs to do small piece of
work.
So one agent did write a story
description like this.
You see that this is a item.
I did change the story description even
it was a story point at the beginning you
see. So then I did answer questions.
You see I did move status back and then
we got new description of story.
Let's see and we have certain story
points.
And you reply to the questions that were
created as a subtask inside this user
Yes, yeah, exactly.
Same as in video you see if you did not
story, right? OK, OK.
see this like I'm showing you some kind
of structure of what we have. Yes.
So now we're focusing a bit on structure,
how, how you need to to track everything.
Yeah. So we have one hour talk, right.
So just to manage time.
Um.
Yes, Sir. Go ahead, please.
Mm-hmm. Can you hear me?
Yes.
So essentially you're creating a some
sort of replication of the team's sub
channels within each ticket to handle
communication with the bot.
With the help of questions and answers.
Is that correct understanding?
Not really the goal of the.
So first of all,
like it's kind of like simulation of real
refinement.
So or or grooming if I got your question
like that's why if you have story we want
to develop it,
AI has access to the development code and
then it raises a question if AI is
properly understand the task.
We could even like first run the question
iteration and then run like agent which
is to write in the stories and we could
probably reduce one step but like again
like I'm just testing it for now it it
kind of simulation and also this is
needed to.
Build some kind of like borders for the
agent which will then design solution and
then borders for the agent which will be
will develop the code. This is important.
If I got your question correctly. If not,
just rephrase please.
Right, right, right.
But but I mean you you answered
essentially yes,
because as a for example business analyst,
I would engage either in live meeting
right or in chat conversation with.
Customer in order to elicit requirements
or refine the understanding, right? So OK.
Yeah,
but also not sure about your customers.
Usually my customers,
my product owners are super busy if even
me like if you write me a question in the
team chat like.
So in most about the work,
like in most of the cases,
I don't know context.
I need to have JIRA ticket.
What is trigger the question like because
I can do some whatever I can do in
parallel. Yeah,
so same happens with product owners with
whom I did work on enterprise projects.
They usually are busy.
They they want to have separate meeting.
Mhm.
They want to have separate meeting where
they go through through stories,
read the questions, provide you answers.
So even like currently we have Anna Dodin
Yeah.
in the project, so she she she's.
Basically can cook in morning.
She can drink coffee and she can answer
questions which we do raise in Jira
ticket like so like.
Yeah,
so it was not to to to as a reductionist,
right or as a kind of oh,
it's just it is team channel, right?
It it is just that you are bringing the
team channel functionality within the
And yeah.
context which teams channel would not
have normally and you would have to bring
the context to the team channel.
Over here you're bringing the.
The capability of bringing,
keeping the conversation going within the
context itself, right? So,
so that is the difference. OK, great.
Yes, probably if I got you right.
So teams channels are cannot be recorded.
Yeah, happened.
They have limited time of history.
First of all,
OK, well sorry.
I I I don't like team communication and
decisions making in teams at all.
Because it's not recorded at all.
Like for good if you have kind of
approved step in workflow by your
customer,
then you can record decisions and state
this is in the story.
But what I saw in most cases you don't
have it. So same here.
I cannot proceed without answer questions.
Yes or I can, but I can expect.
Exam.
You, you,
you usually people saying like
hallucinations,
but I would say creativity.
So if I would not answer questions and AI
can behave as it decides, yes, so like.
Like with questions I I I do put limits
here.
So the next step here also just an
example solution design.
Yeah go ahead Vera.
Just a just a minute. Yep.
We have a question from Maxim Marks. Hi,
dear.
Yeah, sure. Hi colleagues. I'm wondering,
Lodimir,
where will you get the historical data to
story point the user stories correctly?
Because from my experience as a BA,
in order to story point,
even if we have a context for AI,
we need historical data and other similar
project or otherwise like this story
point.
Does it make a lot of sense?
I I do agree with you.
So basically here the context for story
points was this one.
Template for story template.
And this is.
This is template for AI which it uses and
I did observe that that works.
I mean like if the store goes to this
bucket then it's really complex in most
of the cases.
There is I do not use historic but
answering your question in in in correct
way you you you should have another agent
if you want to really go to details.
Yeah so and we did build it more more
than one year ago and it works by the way
even with G PT4.
So we did estimate like stories.
We did provide estimations of stories
with story points with short descriptions
and agent needed to answer a new story
and what I did I I like.
Did hide like some story and asked the
agent to estimate it based on the other
stories and just go went one by one and
the estimations from agent were much
better than by humans in some cases for
human.
Underestimated things,
but agent explained why it's high and
when I did recheck manually the full
request,
it was really more than expected initial
estimation.
Also some interesting observation,
but good good point. Yes,
source data for story points should be
there, so like.
Because you know,
like each month as soon as we are getting
better and better models.
We can write worse quality of prompts.
Because one agent then can perform
multitasking.
So in our case it performs story
description plus story estimation.
Separate agent performs questions, right?
So basically 2 agents only.
Half of year before or one year before,
I would do 3 items, one for story points,
another one for for, for, for, for,
for descriptions or one for questions.
Yeah, in the way for for solution design,
we perform description of solution design
and we perform.
It also one agent now,
but before I would do this with two
agents because what is the problem here?
Because this agent is doing a description
of story and diagram and it is currently
in one Jason file which.
Is by default can be broken.
So for sure AI is fixing it,
but overall it's not really a good way.
If you're talking about kind of super
production, then it is 2 agents.
One is writing description,
second is writing diagram.
It's two different MD files when we then
we are taking one.
Result for story description and we are
taking another one for diagram.
Why diagram is separate field again same
story I can do like for instance if I
want AI to.
To give me all structure like.
SD API for instance.
And here when I I will ask for for for
the data,
I can just give AI one field instead of
description I can give summary and
diagrams.
So and then diagrams will eat mass less
tokens than descriptions because you see
description is is really heavy but
diagrams it's pretty short one and it
gives understanding of the system
immediately.
I hope you you you got my idea. If not,
ask questions, please.
Oh.
That's why we're here.
Would be great to have the rendering of
diagrams right here.
Yeah.
That's why, to be honest.
You can you see this, but yeah,
I I just did not finish it to be honest,
but even did publish it to to Web Store
in Google.
In video what I saw it was extension.
So basically if you're in Jira in Chrome
you you could click a button and then the
button needs to visualize this one.
But I think there is compilation issue or
some during publishing because I did not
check this one zip.
I can share it, you can try it,
even you can fix it if you have time.
By the way,
the idea of this extension was really to
draw diagram in your UI just via regex.
I did quite put it in several hours,
so that's why not sure if it will work
perfectly,
but it should support Chrome and Safari.
Got it. Uh, yeah. For now you get, yeah.
Umm.
Well, a question from Nina. Nina. Hello.
Hello, my dear.
Yeah, Ira,
I think you can skip my question because
Yeah.
I don't want to hijack Vladimir's time.
Yeah, but that's fine.
We have 45 minutes I just see.
OK, OK.
So I think we will be able to build JIRA
structure. But guys, like you,
you can raise your hands if you know how
to build JIRA structure because that's
what I wanted to show you as well.
Who? Who?
Who from you has a like admin rights?
Binjira.
OK, some guys, yes, but most of you know,
to be honest, like I don't have,
I do have rights to create automations in
customers, Jiras, etc.
So that's why like all the changes in
Jiras, usually it's pain,
but that's why I did introduce.
My Jira,
so I'm paying for it now for like for
each account you need to pay I think $9
probably or something.
It was today was some received $27.
00 per month. I can explain why.
If you have one account,
even 2 because you need to have account
for yourself and you need to have account
for AI teammate. So you you have this one.
Here we have me, Ira and AI,
so three accounts.
You will pay for each account separately,
like if I will add one more,
so I will pay more.
So that's why usually I think we will not
add nobody to to to our projects yet.
Why I need to pay?
Because if you use automations,
it was a bit surprise for me.
This one you have limits.
And the automations are really important
for for running of the part because we
need to really to to to to split things
which we are delegating to AI and which
we are keeping with automations so.
For instance adding labels automation
like just simple if subtask summary
starts from this and this we extract and
label and add in label.
So this is automation, but for each run,
let's say we are paying.
So then ticket creations automatically,
etc. So all of these it is automations.
You have limits. Now we have.
1000 runs of automations per month with
this tariff.
What we are using this is basic one.
Initially I think you have two hundreds.
So that's why if you don't want to pay
for it,
I decided to pay because I I'm lazy.
It's not like to develop.
Polling solution will cost more times
than to just to pay this $20,
but overall you can have this one or if
it does not allowed by by your customer
then you can use polling solution.
What means polling?
In that case you have JIRA as it is,
but you have runner which is pinging the
JIRA JQLS for request for work like I
have.
For instance,
Jira filter like and assignee in Vladimir.
OK.
Okay. Yes.
OK,
nothing but overall let's do this report.
I think I did create something. Yes,
so you can use this is like input filter
and when AI finishes the work for
instance or you did some other magic you
need to just for instance.
Change reporter,
add label or whatever just to exclude
items from the filter and then you will
have polling model.
So when your AI job for instance running
each 5 minutes it checks input with tasks.
Take one from the list, do the work,
add label at the end to remove the task
from the list and the same for others and
then each 5 minutes if there is no work
it will be just running and do nothing,
but if there is some new work it will get
it automatically.
So in our post scenario we have
combination,
we have automations and polling model.
So depending on scenario because for
instance we can create some Adobe task,
translations, content.
We also have sharing priorities like if
product owner changing.
Priority for instance on story level,
all priorities on subtasks also changing
like if some story become a blocker or
need to be done yesterday.
So in the case all priorities will be
restructured,
all board will be restructured.
So it's also kind of automation what can
be run here.
So that's why Jira has limitations,
but to play with this it will be enough.
So that's why probably you will get the
things that not all time I'm using AI
teammate to do the work because sometimes
I'm doing completely the same but
directly from Corsor.
Because like so from one angle I just
save money.
Like I don't run automations from other
angle I'm getting speed because I know
exactly what is needed.
I have comments and I just run the same
but from course or.
Yeah and by the way at the end on on Jira.
So when I did run it in GitHub I think
here yes you see this pull request I have
it's done but I need to review it.
So in my local git and then I will
publish it.
So but it was created with all summaries.
Blah blah blah etcetera.
It was from 1 iteration.
Basically exactly this one was from 1
iteration. 25 files change it. Cloud 3.7.
So you can read it. By the way,
if you want how how to read messages from
Jira or sorry teams. OK, let's come back.
Important.
You have projects,
you see that that's playground.
I created it to run integration tests
because because I do development with AI,
all step after AI need to be checked.
I can do this manually or I can write
scripts. So that's why I did ask AI to.
Write scripts to check itself.
So when I'm running integration tests AI
creates tickets in this project and
removes this after it.
So that's why if I I think create some
new ticket here.
It should be some some really quick ID.
Yes, 795 here.
So structure you have there is a button
you have usually OK they probably changes
something.
Space.
Yes, work types.
Here you can edit so epic task subtask so
you can add new bug for instance.
All admin people have it.
You need to understand this part as well
because like there is nothing super crazy.
Yeah,
so it's just easy and UI there is you can
customize the fields.
So if someone saying we cannot add some
field to the Jira, do not trust this guy.
They can. You don't know right people.
You need to explain why you need the
field and then you need to find some
admin people. Usually enterprises.
They have separate teams who are who are
responsible for it and they can do this
magic for you, for instance.
Bug does not have priority. OK,
I just can it here diagrams. OK, cool.
I want to get OK not here,
but in description fields a priority I
want to have on the right side.
There is we have you see original
estimates, time tracking, etcetera. Yeah,
pretty simple and you have it.
So we have issue type bug workflow added
again the same.
So this workflow what I did introduce
this workflow is enough for currently for
for for for the purposes of my project.
Important to mention here usually in
enterprises.
They try to limit people in workflows
because if you have separate workflow for
different projects,
then they need to first of all pay more
money. Second,
they need to spend more time on support.
Because like that's why in Postel
sometimes we we have crazy behaviour when
someone is adding new workflow and or
restructuring the workflow they can
affect multi projects and it is a problem.
But again editing of the workflow is
pretty simple there is.
Status we can edit, we can name it,
create new one,
we can mark it and we can build with
arrows like full scenario cause I do use
same workflow for all issue types.
I did not freeze this scenario so I
wanted to move tickets in view whatever
status I want.
And not many people on the project in the
case. And to be honest,
I don't expect many people in AI native
teams.
It it it should be a limited amount of
people who who who can play with this and
that people need to have access.
To build this workflow as they be want.
Yes, Asha, go ahead please.
Just interrupt me and say.
No,
I just wanted to say that in in in the
real world when you're working for quite
a big enterprise project where you have
many different teams in it, right,
you most probably won't be having such
luxury to change the workflow,
change the issue type composition,
etcetera,
etcetera and it is dedicated for some
specific.
Academy group and it would be quite,
quite hard to believe me.
Thanks.
I remember the story from Liberty Global.
Yeah, I I I did the same.
Successful story.
I I also introduced the question tickets
and it was pretty successful.
But right now I have an opposite actually
experience when I have some advanced.
Level of access to Jira,
but I completely I'm not really
authorized to make any changes because it
will impact some other teams.
So I I'm not blocking the idea itself
about the flexibility.
And.
No, no, no, no. That's really valid one.
That's that's really one good question
I believe this is not the intention.
Yeah.
because I forgot also to mention over
crowds.
That's exactly what I was looking for.
Yeah, so yes.
So if you are not allowed to change it,
I I hope who guys who did work on liberty.
We did work with guy Alegrafimovic and he
said like guys why we need to change
something like or use separate fields if
we have labels.
So then like if you don't have
permissions to change workflow all time,
you can have labels and play with them as
you wish.
You can use labels as workflow as you
want. Yeah, so like again,
this is first straightforward,
a bit stupid.
OK.
To distinguish between statuses.
Why it's needed?
Because the triggers for the agents we
need to to make them clear.
So when to call each agent,
when to call agent for description,
when to call agent for solution design,
when to call agent for development.
So this is separation you need to have.
So that's why labels it's one way.
Second way again subtasks.
Even I don't fan of that subtasks to be
honest,
but I when I did build this picture so I
did find that OK that can be used
everywhere.
So this preface is it's something what
you can use.
And to be honest,
I don't remember the cases when subtasks
were blocked.
Even in my teams,
I did not allow to use subtasks because
that did not make sense for me.
But what I remember in each project,
even in EPAM server,
I would say legacy JIRA,
it's still also there.
You can even build your workflow just on
subtasks and this preferences.
So same As for me,
you see the ticket right then subtasks.
Questions solution design development.
You want QA, QA.
You want more components as the API, SDUI,
API, UI, Microservers A, Microservers B,
Microservers C, whatever.
One of the case Rally has limitation on
to any workflows. I did use all of them,
but in Rally it was basically a good
thing in tracker.
So that really you can have you can have
20 workflows,
you can have good structure and you can
build also basically.
I understand what I'm just explained here
with Rally as it is with GitHub issues.
To be honest, I don't know.
Would would would happy to see this,
but at least look into to to my part here
like I don't know we we definitely have
labels.
I see projects, milestones,
probably there is some customer
realizations, transfer issues, duplicate,
something probably as well possible.
But sub issues already means that even in
the GitHub structure you can replicate
structure what I just did show.
With story description, questions,
solution design and development.
Hope did answer,
but if you have some more crazy scenarios,
let me know I I can try to help.
For instance,
in free version you cannot use a lot of
relationships.
Not free even,
but like it's only is blocked by
duplicated and relates and you cannot
create a new or at least I did not find
how but playing with this it will be your
first homework create AI account.
In Gmail or whatever else service you
want, create your JIRA project.
Start to build the structure like I just
did show.
Try it then in confluence page try to
build the the pages.
You see the structure on my side.
Yes I did describe everything here,
not by hand for sure, but by AI.
So like I have structure you see by AI to
mate it was created in August or updated
in August. Here are here descriptions.
This is all was created after discussion
with Opus.
Also definitions of UI framework also
here.
Again, this is long text,
mostly not for me.
I know how it's structured,
but I don't know in details.
If you ask me, OK Vova,
give me like template of the story. No,
I will not tell you but.
I say OK,
should be acceptance criterias etc.
If you ask me OK,
Vova give me template for solution design.
I can tell you one thing here that
definitely AI needs to say what is
already done in the app.
AI needs to match solution to acceptance
criterias. This is important part here.
If you look to description you can see
existing feature endpoints for instance
for API.
Again just to be sure that AI will not be
creative and will not create new one.
So then implementation details.
And you see this is also markdown.
It's general markdown syntaxes,
which is required here because ZEP pages
again, they're not used by me,
it's used by AI.
When you're building AI native team,
first of all you need to think that
everything what will be done by AI in the
Jira in in in in GitHub whatever it will
be it it need to be understandable by AI.
So that's why you need to understand how.
AI is reading it.
Like maybe move to this point later I
think in details more.
So here we can see implementations that
then we can see this part which is really
important,
which is to be honest in production I
never see this.
Like acceptance one mapping to solution X,
acceptance 2 mapping to solution Y and
etcetera.
If like or for instance mapping to
question tickets like all all decisions,
why is acceptance criteria is created
because we have question ticket with some
decision of product.
Usually people will say, oh,
I'm sorry for business analyst,
but like I need to create all the
question tickets manually. No,
I will not do this. OK, create automation.
Like which will do like create question
ticket which will create subtask and link
this to the story.
Like just we'll show you because I'm not
lying here.
It's my playground and my PC one favorite
so we have button.
Create task or question and here we can
see like OK if if it's product owner,
if I ask it I have question.
If I mark it, it will block my ticket,
so when I click create.
Yeah, Anna is on vacation from today,
so I hope she will not read it,
but it it should be.
She will definitely get the notification.
I hope no. So you see like it's created,
it's blocked by its PO prefix.
Vladimir,
is it the way how today your business
And.
analyst communicate with Pure Pure?
That what I I asking them to do all the
time. That how not not all the time.
It would be really cool if they would
state all questions in the ticket
descriptions.
But that how guys did it in Liberty
Global even developers they did create
tickets for business analyst for solution
architecture.
Yeah, but but yeah, the question here,
how they will manage like backlog of
Questions.
questions your items in case you will
have large scale project with an
Did you see the?
extensive list of ethics and in a role of
a BA?
Uh.
Yeah,
usually you cover plenty of questions
within 5 minutes,
10 minutes call with the client and you
That's cool. Yeah, I I got the questions.
It's pretty great.
don't need to manage these items. Uh-huh.
So like this basically was it's by the
way topic for another one hour,
but like the the questions were
introduced I think in 2017.
Some some in Liberty Global first time.
The reason was like this.
I I I'm remember the case when I did ask
business analyst.
Don't don't remember the name like when
you answer one question XYZ.
And I got answer like your question in
list of 1000 questions in my my mailbox.
Why I need to answer your question in
first view?
And it was valid point how to understand
which question has higher priority.
So that's why you see that question is
linked to the parent automatically.
The parent has fixable.
Just have a call,
just have a a call and transcript and
No, no, no, no. Nina, Nina,
you did not work with me on the project.
generate and for your.
You will not have time for calling with
all people in in in pretty good interpret.
Yeah,
but I was working as a BA for 15 years.
That's OK. We can discuss it. Like, look,
let me explain.
Ira knows already.
If she wants to schedule Colin Post and L
probably if if she's lucky,
she will schedule next week.
If she wants to to to to find someone
else,
let's say who is who has higher title for
instance, 2 weeks or even 3.
Sometimes we did wait for the whole two
months.
So depending on the level with whom you
need to talk.
So again here you have a story or feature
you have priorities of this,
then priorities of the story feature will
be immediately transferred to the
question.
Will be fixed version priority and all of
the relationship.
I don't want to show now BA board,
but be sure that there is BA tickets
which are sorted in logical queue in the
way how they need to work.
For instance story which is now in the
testing and the testing team has
questions will be on.
At the top of their list features which
they need to work on.
Next Pi will have less priority than
questions from dev team now.
So and this is a way of working
priorities, crossing priorities,
automations, etc. All of this is.
Approved and established it by all teams.
If tomorrow I I'm raising the question if
I'm going to the board and then I I know
that this question will be in the top
list. If tomorrow I will not get answer,
I can get to go to a business analyst or
solution architect and ask what did you
do?
You did not work on top priority item in
your list and it is a problem.
I hope you got my principle here,
so if you're building the right structure
as I'm shown here.
Let's switch to support like this.
Top level story level this then you have
fixed versions with dates which sortable
field and priority.
So fixed version release date basically
priority.
And yeah, that's it.
2 fields is enough to sort your work.
You all the time know what task you need
to do first.
I can share this in in practice if if you
want,
but it's a bit another topic but like now
we are talking.
So this is needed by the way because we
are working with human.
Let's see in the way when we are working
with agents like we are shown here.
This is prioritization.
I don't see that is really needed,
to be honest, because bottleneck, it's me.
I cannot generate ideas or I cannot
answer questions faster than AI is doing
the work.
of work.
Me is bottleneck.
But once some context is generated by AI,
you will need time to review it.
So.
Yes,
and I do measure and I'm waiting for the
Right.
time when I will not make any corrections.
With Solnet 4.
5 I almost don't do corrections at all.
So I I I'm correcting several things
which I want to to to to do AI in the.
Way how I did it before,
but it suggests another way.
So but in most of the cases I'm still in
control of architecture.
I'm in control of project administration,
stories, priority, stories, descriptions,
acceptance, categories.
But I'm losing control on actual
development. I'm not losing it.
How to say I'm delegating it.
Yeah.
Yeah, Thomas.
For what we have free questions. Yeah.
Thomas, please.
Yes.
So after a certain volume of questions,
there will be the need of prioritizing
questions, right?
No.
I mean there there will be multiple
people raising high priority questions,
then there will be the the issue that I
think my question is more important than
yours.
No, it will not be the.
How to say?
Yeah.
You may want to say that it will be also
delegated.
Yeah,
so like now we have mix mix of scenario
like about project admin and let's say
agentic for flow.
In agentic for flow when agents are
raising questions to me, let me go here.
You see there is this priorities.
It was designed like this and really if
we go to to the let me show you this
script, not script but instructions.
OK, it's a bit slower today. Agents.
It's open source if you want to,
let's say, step in and run faster.
So feel free to use this repo story
questions.
So you see it's like it it it has
priorities already in this yes like this
allowed priorities.
So and this is description how we we have
template on the question.
We have kind of request,
we have template of markdown for AI do
not mix and like really important to to
say several times for AI template to Jira
markdown not just markdown because most
of the AI was like in the like in the
knowledge base it was.
Markdowns from GitHub.
So that's why it's really wants to use
markdown instead of Jira markdown.
By the way, for GitHub,
if you use GitHub as a tracker,
then marked out, it's super cool. Yeah,
so then there is just.
Questions. So we have empty array,
but by the way cloud 4.
5 it has questions all the time,
so that's why I do not run it all the
time. I do limit it for one only,
but overall we can run it how many times
we want. And yes,
you see that it investigates codebase
first before raising any.
Questions for understanding of images,
we use Gemini because I cannot read
images for now, for today. And yes,
no duplications, blah blah blah.
It is like instructions how to raise the
questions and I'm saying about priorities,
but I'm not defining when to use which
priority because usually it's a way of
working from my side.
It's like I'm I'm writing a story waiting
for description and questions.
I can play with Kate, I can drink coffee,
I can be on the meetings, whatever.
So then I'm reading the description,
I'm reading questions,
providing answers because like if
descriptions completely wrong,
then my mistake was in the first input of
the story. So.
Then when I answer a question again
reging your rate description and this is
most important part acceptance criterias
and questions because myself I'm reading
I I'm reading like diagram mermaid
diagram for solution design.
To understand real concept and on high
level,
just briefly I'm reading like classes
which will be affected and functionality
which is exist. So because why?
Because I did not change it.
That's very important to have
measurements all the time if you don't
change description of solution design.
Probably you don't need to read it,
except you need to understand it.
So that's why I'm saying that at some
point this step can be skipped at some
point depending of like.
Depending when, yeah.
So here we are talking about technical
aspects and I I want you and again myself,
when we are doing this for customers,
we must be responsible for it,
for artifacts which is generated even by
AI, we are responsible for it.
That's why human in control.
We are proving solution,
we are proving pull request.
So you see is a pull request created for
teams integration.
We can see here already today it's super
slow.
We we can see the description and we have
already review from Corsor bot and I
think from Gemini as well.
So something from Copilot.
So now three guys are reviewing me,
not me, but another AI, Gemini,
Copilot and Corsor.
Full stack entropic code I need to
connect then will be full stack.
Dmitry, please.
Yes, yes, Vladimir.
If I may summarise what we saw here,
this is this is a solution for you know,
agenda enhancements of specifically a
requirement elicitation and work tracking
in the team,
not focusing on coding specifically,
right. And my question, not yet.
Not yet.
My question would be what kind of of of?
Improvements in terms of team
productivity you observed, for instance,
less meetings for BAS,
more streamlined focus time for
developers.
Basically how you were able to measure
the improvements or benefits of of
adopting this.
AI agenting tooling for for productivity.
Yeah so for for for this approach what I
am showing here it's example of DM tools.
Basically this is open source project
which is I connected to Jira and just did
built everything what I wanted to show
you capabilities of current environments
tools to show those.
The full pipeline here I can tell you
that like that from May I did not write
code myself at all.
I did not write store descriptions at all.
I can prove it with all metrics,
I just do.
Validation of AI work and again like now
except of just was idea to connect to
teams and build my own personal assistant
with super cool organised second brain in
scope of KB and blah blah blah etcetera.
I would even probably not develop this
connector to teams.
Because I did not have other ideas
regarding real production,
there is a lot of a lot of dependencies
of people on people.
The main problem that people cannot do it
in the way how I am doing it.
They don't trust.
They don't update the rules because when
I run the agent and that did something
stupid, I'm going and updating the rules.
Just just an example like for story
description there is even in the rules
like.
Let me again show you.
Story description this one.
Yeah this this line don't write in head
store description of ticket.
It was added because AI all the time.
I don't know why but that did write like
enhance store description of ticket
ticket XYZ.
So I just added it because I was too lazy
to remove it all the time.
Yeah so like this is this is the way how
I I do it once and then I'm getting it as
I want all the time was the the the the
problem when other peoples are using they
they do try button.
Probably that works. That's good.
Say to use it or workflow or the agent.
If it does not work,
they just stop to use it.
Then Ira is jumping to the process and
adoption process. She's talking to people.
She's understanding what works,
what does not work, why it does not work.
Explains where the rules,
how to add the rules,
how to use it properly. Yeah,
how to adjust process.
To use the agents.
So it's it's kind of combinations that's
why like benefits we have a numbers you
can talk to me from post NL we have a
numbers so usually we share this in
reports you you can get it but from post
NL side we we did not run coding agents.
What we are showing here we we don't have
permissions yet to run agent Celia agent
which has access to code base like cursor
or entropic code code and this is a power
here in this command.
Because my business analyst has access to
the code base,
my solution architect also has access to
code base,
but they are acting in different role.
So this is important to understand.
I guess things that actually you
highlighted one of the problems we we try
to solve with our clients with AI
consultancy is how to upskill people to
to use properly the AI tooling and yeah
this is.
It's another storyline.
Let's say it's about adoption and it's
more about human mindset processes as
well, agile transformation,
engineering excellence.
So it's all of this is connected.
I'm showing combination from technical
aspect.
But this combination will not work if
people don't understand it.
So that's why combination is in place,
Maxim.
Yeah,
for just a question in the chat regarding
how did you measure,
but I'm interesting if you're following
that,
maybe it's like just how you're doing the
Let me show judge, judge,
look just quickly. This is this, this is.
projects and you're having this question
Jira type,
but I can insert the prompt injection
into the question.
I'm sorry, let me let me show you.
This is report.
Of AI agent in post NL.
Artifacts which are generated by AI and
post NL. So there is weeks.
So at the end it all the time low.
But like we know people,
we know what they're doing,
which artifacts are generating and
etcetera like it's one of their report.
Yes, we do not split series even.
So.
This metrics are collected from JIRA.
We have one script, let's say.
We can connect it to the JIRA.
We can explain I I can tell you that in
my team how many 5-5 test cases were only
created manually for instance,
because people are using AI and all the
metrics we are checking from history.
So where we are taking Jira tickets,
we are taking history.
We we know what exactly do what and we
are measuring it.
You can do it also as well yourself
probably manually because like or via via
DC by the way as well.
That's why I also started from you need
to have AI teammate or AI agent or
whatever else name you will introduce.
Separate account which will act as you in
Post ML.
We're using my personal account from Post
ML because nobody did allow us yet to
create this AI teammate and connect it to
the JIRA.
So that's why we even in the script we we
are using like OK if that is related to
test cases.
I never created test cases so that we can
trust this that it was not from me but it
was from AI.
Also AI is writing like comments like
kind of AI response like this.
Then we also understand usage and that it
was not me but it was AI.
So we are measuring.
So all part there is processed.
I don't remember how many tickets but a
lot like 10,
000 or even 15 to to to get this chart
with real data and there is kind of if
you're talking about pricing we we more
should should focus on outcome based
model.
We're not saying like how my team
velocity will be increased.
I cannot commit on the numbers.
I can tell you how many test cases AI
will create or how many test or how many
descriptions AI will write.
What people will do during these
activities, drink coffee,
talk to other people or whatever else
that I cannot commit.
So like this is the difference.
We can say what agents can do and how
much money this work is caused by human.
And then you can calculate do simple
maths. OK,
I need to create this case one minute or
two minutes or five. I don't know.
OK then how many?
Let's say how much time you need to check
10,000 of this cases.
To find potential regression issues,
one hour 2.
Yeah, is it?
OK,
but how will you measure measures this
time? Like in case if I've generated,
let's say 100 user stories,
It's depending on your project.
how will you automatically?
But how we will you on your project?
How you measuring?
How much time did people spend to the
reviewing the outcome from LLM?
I see like so they they they don't write
it, yes. So same as me, I don't write it.
Mm-hmm.
So this this is time saving.
First of all they find potential
regression issues,
connections between different
functionality.
So again critical path big one that we
can build in post NL as well because we
have all connected data and like with
edge we can just build it and support in
Mhm.
real time.
So basically this is a power like that
like.
In most of the cases,
if you do it correctly,
you will not have production incidents.
That's also one more metric because like
we have all the relationship,
we we find all potential regression
issues because we have conducted test
cases.
You will not have production incidents
because team will test everything before
going to production.
Yeah,
so it's also some kind of metric which
you cannot calculate. By the way,
you can talk to Andrei Stotsky.
He he did calculate even this how that
impacts on on the PNL, et cetera.
But like the model is different here.
I'm not talking about like.
Definitely review of the test case is
less time than to write the test case.
For me,
even when I calculated in the check
descriptions, need to recalculate.
By the way,
we did use similarity of descriptions
based on the history.
882 persons was the same.
So what AI did fried,
it was set in the stones.
Nobody did change it.
So I think now it should be more because
when we did use a calculation we did use
GPT 5 at 3.5 and GPT 4.
Now we use trip clot for so the person
should be higher.
Of test cases accepted by human
immediately.
That's why like depending on team,
depending on test case,
someone someone wants to to to write big
test case, someone small one.
How much time you spend on formatting?
A lot of asects.
We can see it with timer and check like
OK AI did write test case,
QA did read it or QA did write test case
manually etcetera.
But how to calculate like OK QA did find
all related test cases?
From his head or at least whatever,
probably he will use JQL or something
else and AI did did this exercise.
What is penalties if QA skipped this or
AI skipped this?
Question mark.
So basically there is some sort of undal
law to the limits of the parallelization,
You know you is it's you're going through.
right?
Because if you want to keep the humans as
complements, right,
kind of part of the process,
human in the loop.
There are some limits to the speed up
that you can achieve by outsourcing this,
right? That's what you're trying to say.
Unless we get rid of unreliable humans,
Yeah.
we cannot scale unlimitlessly, right?
I can tell you my personal experience,
so here.
When you're trying to do in this agentic
flow multi projects.
You you getting crazy,
let's say in two hours or three.
So I did try to run 4 and then when I
switched between windows I already forgot
what exactly I did or I did ask to do.
So it is a problem when you're focusing
on one project then it's better.
So while AI writing solution for one
ticket,
you already can write story for new
ticket.
Then when you did finish writing story
for new ticket,
you come back to previous one and just
reviewing this while AI is writing there.
But again it's a lot of question to human
what you will do.
Will you really switch between activities
like this or not?
It's it's like my my velocity boost
cannot be applicable for your velocity
boost.
And vice versa. Or for instance,
today it can be applicable,
but not tomorrow,
because today I will switch between tasks,
but tomorrow I will play with my kid.
But for instance,
like I can do the work with my laptop in
Cursor,
but now I also can play in in some kids
room with with this kid and do all the
work from my phone with just directs.
This.
With AI teammate.
So like how to like how to consider this
boost like a lot of side effects. Again,
that's why I'm usually saying we need to
think only what what we can commit.
It is on these artifacts which are
created by AI and we can tell you quality
Bye.
of these artifacts because human usually
do review.
So velocity will be really dependent on
people.
People.
And over today, we have to finish.
I.
Yeah, let me stop screen sharing.
So today as you got it, yeah,
so we did have this intro and mostly
focused on project management.
Let me just write down homework.
So JIRA project set up in the way as I
did show. If you have questions,
feel free to ask.
Confluence it up with template.
Play with Opus.
Try to imagine your scenarios like of
your project.
Try to build something what we did
discuss today.
How to properly get questions,
how to properly answer them,
how to track these activities.
Like how to manage subtasks,
put limitations of your project by the
way and ask Opus to suggest you as a way
how to manage it, etcetera. So cursor.
I would suggest really to install it and
buy license if you did not yet or ask
your account manager GitHub account and
GitHub workspace because next steps will
be like we're going to.
To create website publish it on GitHub
pages.
If you have domain you will just link it
and the I will write it for you like in
the way.
So let's say next time we will create
this story description agent just in
GitHub connect some other.
Let's say also I'm going to show you like
context management,
LLM end points and all of this in details
from technical aspect because you need to
understand how it works behind.
Cursor, GitHub, Jira conference.
Make this prerequisite.
If you talk about accounting Jura,
should it be a service account or just a
normal one?
Yeah, it's for for AI.
I just created,
I just created Gmail and just invites
this Gmail account to my Jira project.
I I don't know.
So it's it's like regular employee.
It's normal, yeah.
Uh, so like the human. OK, mhm, mhm, yeah,
yeah, just normal.
Normal.
And just imagine for instance,
you have this crazy attimate which can do.
Mhm.
Things and it can read your Gmail and
also then like it can authorize itself
and do all the magic. Yeah,
so it's next step when you will say your
teammates in this OW. Yeah, but.
Yeah, just regular account.
You can use your,
but again then you cannot say what was
done by you and what was done by AI.
This is important to collect metrics.
I will show you how to build the reports.
It's also open source by the way.
Next time over next time.
Uh.
Metrics will be part of our topics.
All right guys,
so use this chat right here.
So I think it will be staying here.
So let's let's build there one more
community around the AI topic here.
I I I will again like I will process the
current talk because I said at the
beginning that everything is recorded.
We have a tool.
I will process the current talk.
I will process your messages in the chat.
I will build KB and you will see a really
nice graph.
In Obsidian and also we have another
thing idea how to add connect bot to this
and you will be able to to talk to data
what we just discussed today.
So be here or just disconnect if you
don't want to be processed by AI.
Yeah. Thank you guys.
I will send you invite to next meetings
and see you next week.
Bye.
Thanks much, Vova. Thanks, Zero.
That was amazing.
Thank you very much. Bye.
Thank you. Bye, bye. See you later.
Thanks by the way.
I've got it.
Thank you. Thank you. Bye.
Thank you.